<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "http://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">
<pkgmetadata>
  <use>
    <flag name='convtojpeg'>Use <pkg>media-libs/netpbm</pkg> and <pkg>media-libs/libjpeg-turbo</pkg> to convert screenshots to JPEG.</flag>
    <flag name='figlet'>Use <pkg>app-misc/figlet</pkg> to print number of the last watched episode with big numbers in ASCII-art style.</flag>
    <flag name='parallel'>Use <pkg>sys-process/parallel</pkg> to compress taken screenshots utilizing all available CPU cores.</flag>
    <flag name='pngcrush'>Install <pkg>media-gfx/pngcrush</pkg> to compress PNG screenshots.</flag>
    <flag name='remember-delays'>Pull dependencies required to remember sub-delay and audio-delay between episodes: <pkg>media-video/mpv</pkg>, <pkg>sys-fs/inotify-tools</pkg> and <pkg>sys-process/procps</pkg>.</flag>
    <flag name='toilet'>Same as figlet, but output is colored.</flag>
    <flag name='xdg-open'>Pull <pkg>x11-misc/xdg-utils</pkg> for the dialog suggesting to open RELEASE_NOTES of a newer version online.</flag>
  </use>
  <longdescription>
watch.sh is written to simplify access to video files and play videos easily.
It allows playing single files, DVD/BD folders and folders with episodes
of TV series. For the former and the latter ones it can also find external
subtitles and tracks, applying heuristic algorithms to include files with
names that may strongly differ from the names of corresponding video files,
and that frees you from the job of picking appropriate subtitles manually.

This script can also help you deal with organization taken screenshots,
placing them right into the folder named after video and compressing them
after you stop watching it.

For the folder with episodes watch.sh can track your watching progress,
allowing to run episodes one after another without creating a playlist,
but remembering the episode number you quit watching today, so you could
easily resume watching the folder later.

…and many other accompanying things that make life even lazier.
  </longdescription>
</pkgmetadata>
